londonpass.com 2019-06-03

# London Pass Privacy Policy - Leisure Pass Group

Leisure Pass Group (“LPG”/”we”/”us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully in accordance with UK Data Protection Legislation.  LPG is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office in accordance with that legislation.

**1\. General Privacy Policy**

**1.1        Information collected **

We collect the information you choose to supply to us through enquiry forms purchasing our products and any time you e-mail us.

If you make a purchase on our site after being sent from a Eurostar booking, we will share your email address with them in order to comply with the European Commission Package Travel Directive. Your data will be deleted by Eurostar within 7 days.

**1.2        We also collect information automatically about your visit to our web site.**

The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form, and as such, cannot be used to identify you.

**1.3        ****This** **aggregate** **information is used to:**

  * build up marketing profiles

  * aid strategic development

  * audit usage of the site

**1.4        ****Use of personal information**

We process personal information collected via the London Pass website for the purposes of:

  * providing the best possible service

  * processing any orders you may have made

  * conducting market research surveys

  * running competitions

  * providing you information about products and services offered by The Leisure Pass Group

When purchasing a London Pass, customers from EU countries will be given the choice to opt-in to receive marketing communication by checking a box. These communications include but are not limited to emails, SMS and push notifications, giving information, tips and promotions on upgrades and third party offers relevant to a customer’s trip, and promotions on other city passes. Non-EU customers will have the option to uncheck a box to opt out from receiving these communications. All recipients can unsubscribe from marketing communication at any time, by clicking on the unsubscribe process included in every message.

**1.5       ** **Your personal rights and how to contact us**

You have certain rights under existing data protection legislation including the right to request a copy of the personal information we hold about you, if you request it from us in writing.

From May 2018 you will have the following rights:

  1. **Right to access** : the right to request copies of your personal information from us;
  2. **Right to correct** : the right to have your personal information rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete;
  3. **Right to erase:** the right to request that we delete or remove your personal information from our systems;
  4. **Right to restrict our use of your information** : the right to ‘block’ us from using your personal information or limit the way in which we can use it;
  5. **Right to data portability** : the right to request that we move, copy or transfer your personal information; 
  6. **Right to object** : the right to object to our use of your personal information including where we use it for our legitimate interests or where we use your personal information to carry out profiling to inform our market research and customer demographics  (see section 5 above).

To make enquiries, exercise any of your rights set out in this Privacy Policy and/or make a complaint please contact our Customer Services Team at [dataprotection@leisurepassgroup.com](mailto:dataprotection@leisurepassgroup.com)

If you are not satisfied with the way any complaint you make in relation to your personal information is handled by us then you may be able to refer your complaint to the relevant data protection regulator which in the UK is the Information Commissioner’s Office.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed and construed in all respects in accordance with the laws of England and Wales.

**How long do we keep your personal information?**

We will hold your personal information on our systems indefinitely or until you request it is deleted. Even if we delete your personal information it may persist on backup or archival media for legal, tax or regulatory purposes.

**2.            THE LONDON PASS APP**

2.1        When you download the London Pass App (“the App”), synchronise your London Pass with the App, or purchase the Mobile Pass, LPG will ask you for certain information including your name, phone number, postal address, email address and contact details. LPG may also record which services you are interested in as well as patterns of use and information requested by you and offers purchased.  LPG will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

2.2        All personal information will be kept securely in accordance with our internal security policy and will be used to:

(a)        administer, run and enable your use of the App and the Mobile Pass and any Special Offers and/or Pass Holder Offers;

(b)        open and run your account and provide you with an up to date service;

(c)        generally, run the product and its related services.

2.3     Marketing Communications: 

(a)        As an integral part of the App and the services LPG provides, once you have synchronized your London Pass or purchased your Mobile Ticket, from time to time you will receive communications from LPG by SMS, email or via the App about developments concerning offers, promotions, discounts, events and new services or related activities we think you may find useful, together with location specific offers.

(b)        Whilst your personal data will not be passed to third parties these communications may concern services or related activities that other reputable companies that we select, wish to offer to you. (Note that if do contact any such third parties LPG has no responsibility for any arrangements you make with them and any personal data that you provide to such companies will be governed by the terms of their privacy policies.)

**3.            COOKIES**

We use cookies on our website and in relation to the App.  For details of our cookie policy please refer to our **[Cookie Policy](https://www.londonpass.com/cookies.php)**

## Trusted by over 3 million customers, here's what they have to say
